cerberusapp.com 2015-03-27

# Cerberus Privacy policy

LSDroid ("We", "Our") values the privacy of our customers, users, and others who use our mobile device software applications (the "LSDroid Software"), websites, services, and content (e.g., widgets, feeds, and applications) owned or operated by LSDroid (the "LSDroid Services" ). The following Privacy Policy governs the LSDroid Services. 

GENERAL INFORMATION

This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected through the LSDroid Services. LSDroid provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the LSDroid Services.   
This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the LSDroid Terms of Service. Your use of the LSDroid Services and any personal information you provide on the LSDroid Services remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and the Terms of Service. 

IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES AND CONSENTS

Some of the LSDroid Services require the use of SMS text messages. Standard data and messaging charges, fees, and taxes from your wireless operator apply.   
To provide the LSDroid Services, we collect, maintain, use, and display your personal data and the geographic location of your mobile devices (we call this "location information" or "geo-location").   
In order to subscribe to the LSDroid Services, you must consent to: (a) the use of your devices' location to provide the LSDroid Services to you, including the display and disclosure of your location information (b) receive SMS messages; and (c) pay operator data, messaging, and other fees resulting from LSDroid Services usage. 

THE INFORMATION LSDROID COLLECTS

REGISTRATION INFORMATION: You provide to LSDroid certain personally-identifiable information (such as device ID number, wireless operator / operator, your name, email address, etc.) when choosing to subscribe to the LSDroid Services.   
LOCATION INFORMATION: To provide the LSDroid Services, we derive location information from your wireless operator, certain third-party service providers, or directly from the mobile device that you used to register with the LSDroid Services. This location tracking of your mobile device may occur even when the LSDroid Services mobile application is not actively open and running, but your location is being securely transmitted and logged in accordance with your privacy and opt-in settings.   
COOKIES, PERSISTENT FILE INFORMATION: When you use the LSDroid Services, we may send one or more cookies (small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters) to your computer. LSDroid may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your web browser and may be used by us during your subsequent visits to the LSDroid Web site. Persistent cookies set by the LSDroid Web site can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings.   
LOG FILE INFORMATION: When you use the LSDroid Services, our servers automatically record certain information about your usage from your mobile device and web browser. These server securely logs may include information such as a mobile device identification number and device identifier, web requests, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, features used in the LSDroid mobile application, the amount of time spent on particular web pages, the dates and times of your requests, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

THE WAY LSDROID USES INFORMATION

LSDroid uses your personally identifiable, registration, and location information to operate, maintain, and provide to you and other Users all of the features and functionality of the LSDroid Service.   
LSDroid uses your personally identifiable, location, and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous log file information) to track and analyze User preferences and trends in order to improve the quality and design of the LSDroid Services and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services.   
LSDroid uses cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the LSDroid Services; (b) provide custom and personalized content, advertisements, and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (d) monitor aggregate usage metrics.   
LSDroid uses your email address from time-to-time for non-marketing or administrative purposes such as sending privacy or security related notices, notifying you of major LSDroid Services changes, or for other customer service purposes.   
LSDroid does not use your personally identifiable information or location information to send commercial or marketing SMS text messages or email messages to you without your express consent or unless if you have opted-in to be part of a specific program or feature in accordance with the applicable LSDroid Services consent procedures. 

WHEN LSDROID DISCLOSES INFORMATION

LSDroid discloses aggregate, anonymous log file and usage information in reports to interested third parties to assist those parties in understanding the usage patterns and performance results of certain advertisements, content, services, promotions, or features. For example, we may provide aggregate-level reports to a partner for the purpose of showing delivery and performance statistics of a specific advertising campaign.   
LSDroid may release personally identifiable, registration, profile, or location information if required to do so by law.   
LSDroid also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable, registration, profile, or location information that LSDroid believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to: enforce our Terms of Service; take precautions against liability; protect Users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; protect the security or integrity of the LSDroid Services; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of LSDroid, Users, or others.   
LSDroid does not share your personally identifiable information or personally-identifiable location information with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your express consent or unless you have opted-in to be part of a specific program or feature in accordance with the applicable LSDroid Services consent procedures. 

YOUR CHOICES

You may update, correct, or delete your profile information at anytime. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

LSDroid uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information that LSDroid receives on your behalf to operate the LSDroid Services or that you transmit to LSDroid and you do so at your own risk. We also cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, ethical, or managerial safeguards.   
If LSDroid learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. LSDroid may post a notice on the LSDroid Services if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. 

IN THE EVENT OF MERGER, SALE, OR BANKRUPTCY

In the event that LSDroid is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control so that the LSDroid Service can continue operations. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we will do everything in our power to protect how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. You will be notified via notice through the LSDroid Services of any such change in ownership or control of your personally identifiable information. 

CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by the "last modified" policy below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the LSDroid Services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. If we decide to change our privacy policies, then we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.   
For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. If we make such material changes to this policy, then we will notify you here in this Privacy Policy, by email, or by means of a notice on the LSDroid Services home page. 

EFFECTIVE DATE, DATE LAST MODIFIED

LSDroid Privacy Policy effective as of April 3, 2011.   
LSDroid Privacy Policy last modified on March 6, 2012. 

CONTACT INFORMATION

Please contact our privacy manager at support@cerberusapp.com with any questions or comments.
